Guide to the Alexander M. Drummond papers, 1917-1956.
Drummond, Alexander M. papers, 1917-1956
- Series XI. Miscellaneous
  - The Dime Speaker, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Why Outdoor Plays are Produced by S. Selden, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - National Collegiate Players Constitution and By-laws Pamphlet, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Pi Epsilon Delta
  - Thompson Manuscript, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Notes and Articles, March, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    The Progressive
  - Misc. Brochures and Publications, 1954 - 1955 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    The Gateway Theatre; Speech; English; Humanities
  - Theatre reviews and clippings from London, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - American Theatre Wing Catalog and Professional Training Program, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Misc. Catalogs and Ads; University Theatre Critiques, 1948 - 1954 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Education, 1923 - 1953 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    Liberal education; African-Americans; Woman; Culture; Speech; Humanities; Major Programs (divided into two folders)
  - Non-Cornell Academic Theatre - Reviews; Brochures; Schedules; Articles, 1923 - 1952 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Ancient Theatre, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
    Egypt
  - Books and Literature, 1947 - 1952 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    Lists; Reviews; Brochures; Newspaper articles and clippings
  - Theatre Abroad, 1936 - 1952 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    London reviews; Abbey Theatre; Italian passion plays; Swedish calisthenics; Soviet drama; Kabuki; Comedie Francaise; Sarte
  - "What Size Cornell?", undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
    Future of Cornell and private universities as enrollment increases; Finger Lakes photos and articles
  - Agents and Schools, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    New York City
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1949 - 1952 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    Misc; Theatre; Literature
  - Ithaca College Drama, 1950 - 1953 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    Playbills; Reviews; Newspaper clippings
  - Ithaca Civic Opera Group, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    Newspaper reviews
  - Ithaca Community Players, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    Reviews; Newsletters; Playbills
  - Local Theatre Activities, 1951 - 1953 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    Reviews; Newspaper clippings; Playbills
  - Professional Theatre, 1946 - 1953 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    Magazine and Newspaper articles; Reviews; Previews
  - Architectural Publications, undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
    Monographs; Public Buildings
  - The American Stage, undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
    Pamphlet; Amateur
  - Book Catalogues and Advertising, 1951 - 1955 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    Book lists; Foreign publications; Electronic equipment; University presses; Brochures
  - The National League of Pen Women, 1938 - 1939 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    Pamphlet
  - Works Progress Administration, February 12, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    Education and Theatre
  - Plays for High Schools, undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Rural and Small Community Entertainment, May, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Manual for all things Theatre, undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Women Who Work in New York, June, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Extension Work in New York in Agriculture and Home Economics, August, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    Cornell Extension Bulletin; 4-H Club; Farm Bureaus; Home bureaus
  - University Extension Services, 1927 - October 24, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    Rural Theatre; High School Plays; Pamphlets
  - Community Drama and Expert Leadership, November, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    Pamphlet; Playground and Recreation Association of America
  - Penn State Players Extension Department, 1923 - 1924 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    Various pamphlets with play lists, information and more
  - Speech, 1948 - January 23, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    Speech education; Brochures; Conferences; Summer sessions
  - Cascadillian Annuals, 1917 - 1919 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous sheet music, 4 diplomas., 1896-ca. 1920 (Box 21)
  - Books on German Theatre; Book of Photographs; Large Photograph of Columbia University Journalism Alumni, May 7, 1934 and undated (Box 23)
    Fuchs; Thesis on Systematic Dramaturgy
  - Two Issues (1913 - 1914) of Cascadillian and Once Upon a Hill scrapbook, 1913 - 1914, 1946 (Box 30)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Kingsley, Sidney. Men in White. Signed by the author.
The Playground. v.13, no.2,4,9 (1919)
The New Yorker. October 2, 1954.
Hatch, Emily Gilchriest, 1897-. On the road to market. Trivandrum: Keston House, 1938.
The Public Speaking Review. Public Speaking Conference of New England and the North Atlantic States.
The Speech Teacher. v.5, no.3 (September 1956).
World premieres: monthly bulletin of the International Theatre Institute. International Theatre Institute. v.1, no.3-6 (1949-1950).